<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="mission">
        <b>Mission</b>
         \n\n
        <p>To develop highly qualified, globally competitive and innovative human
            resource by providing quality Training, applied Research and
            extension and Entrepreneurship skills that are responsive to market demands
        </p>

    </string>

    <string name="vision">
        <b>Vision</b>
         \n\n
        <p>To be the preferred training institution, for technical and vocational skills development.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="mandate">
        <b>Mandate:</b>
         \n\n
        <p>The mandate of the polytechnic is to develop an institution with excellence in teaching, training, scholarship, entrepreneurship, research, consultancy,
            community service and products with emphasis on technology, its development, impact and application within and outside Kenya;</p>
    </string>

    <string name="corevalue">
        <b>Core Values:</b>
         \n\n
       <small>The Kisii National Polytechnic is committed to and will be identified by the following core values.</small>
        \n
       <b>i.Professionalism and Excellence:</b>
        <p>We believe in delivering excellent services using best practices.</p>
        \n
        <b>ii.Creativity and Innovativeness:</b><p> We believe in diversity and inclusion and thus constantly seek fresh approaches, new ideas and different outlooks to achieve success.</p>
        \n
        <b>iii.Team work:</b>
        <p>We all work together courage for the betterment of our institution. </p>
        \n
        <b>iv.Integrity: </b>
        <p>We are committed to acting in an honest, trustworthy, countable and transparent manner in our operations.</p>
        \n
        <b>v.Accountability and transparency:</b>
        <p>We will perform in a manner at all times that makes us accountable, responsible, and answerable to our customers and other stakeholders both external and internal.</p>
    </string>

</resources>